

# IVAN MARTIĆ

# SOFTWARE & WEB DEVELOPER

# CONTACT

- +385 91 200 8778
- Široli 14c 51216 Viškovo Croatia
- s imartic14
- https://imartic.github.io

## TECHNOLOGIES

C# MS SQL SERVER

HTML CSS JAVASCRIPT

JQUERY VUE.JS GIT

TFS ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP

# LANGUAGES

ENGLISH | GERMAN

CROATIAN

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a Software and Web Developer and fresh graduate of Telematics with passion for programming and design. I have over 1 year professional experience as a Software Developer, developing desktop and web applications. Lately I am focusing on Front-end web development and learning about the latest frameworks like Vue and React. When I am not programming, I like to do some design work and sports.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### ALARM AUTOMATIKA

### NOV 2016 - PRESENT

# Working as Software Developer in Research & Development department at Alarm automatika d.o.o. Worked on several different projects and the ones I worked most on are a self-ticketing cashier for parking lots and a web application for event management (ticketing system) and supervision. For development I mainly used C#, JavaScript/iQuery, HTML, CSS and Microsoft SQL

Server.

### **IMPULS ING**

NOV 2015 - JUL 2016

### **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER**

**SOFTWARE DEVELOPER** 

Worked as Software Developer at Impuls ing d.o.o. Responsible for the development of a module for an existing desktop application. Worked with C# and Microsoft SQL Server (Transact-SQL).

# **EDUCATION**

### **POLYTECHNIC OF RIJEKA**

### **BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING, TELEMATICS**

OCT 2012 - MAR 2017

Bachelor's degree in Telematics. Software Development/Engineering (C++, Java, SQL), Automation, Telecommunications, Electrical engineering, System design,...

# TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES WILDAU

NOV 2015 - JUL 2016

## **TELEMATICS**

Exchange semester at TH Wildau. Software project (JavaFX) and German language.